hireup.com.au 2015-05-08

# Privacy Policy | HireUp

HireUp (“HireUp”, “we” or “us”) is committed to respecting the privacy of your information. This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes the personal information we collect through our website platform and mobile applications (the “Site”), and how we collect and use this information.

This Privacy Policy is organized into the following nine sections:  
1\. Collection and Use of Personal Information  
2\. Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information  
3\. Disclosure of Your Information to Third Parties  
4\. Updating and Correcting Information  
5\. Your Choices  
6\. Security of Information  
7\. Age Restrictions  
8\. Changes to Privacy Policy  
9\. Contact Us 

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

Depending on how you use the Site, we may ask you to share personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) with us. Whether you choose to share your personal information is completely up to you, but you may not be able to access some areas of the Site or effectively use its services offered without sharing relevant personal information. Personal information includes any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact or locate you. Examples include your name, address, email address, phone number, age, household information and educational background. Below are some examples of when we collect personal information.

A. Account Information  
When you register as a HireUp site user, either as a Client or Support Worker, we will ask you for information about you, such as your address, email, birth date and phone number. If registering as a Client, we will also ask you for certain information about yourself or the person you are creating a profile for, such as name, date of birth, disability, etc. If you are registering as a Support Worker, we will also ask for your total years of care work experience, your hourly rate(s) and transportation information. We may also send you promotional emails such as newsletters, new service offerings, special discounts and third-party offers. If you would rather not receive promotional emails please see the section below titled “Your Choices.” 

We also use your personal information for administrative purposes, such as addressing account and billing issues, investigating Site issues, including abuse of the Site, responding to user inquiries and enforcing and applying our Terms of Service. We may also contact you by text message solely in connection with the services and only if you opt in to receive text messages by providing your phone number. Other users may also be able to find your profile on the Site by using search parameters that coincide with the personal information you have provided to us. 

B. User Profile  
After you register for the Site, you will have the opportunity to create a personal profile. Your profile may include different information depending on whether you are a Client or a Support Worker. How much information you disclose on your profile is entirely up to you, though at a minimum, your profile will include information you provided to us in the account registration process (though your contact information, as well as certain other information, is disclosed only in the limited manner described below).

i. Clients may include information on their profile about age and special needs of the person requiring a Support Worker. All registered users will be able to view the profile’s photo, first name and location. In addition, other registered Clients and Support Workers can view shared connections and affiliations.  
ii. Support Workers may include information about their hourly rates, background, availability, education, and relevant certifications, qualifications and experience, and any geographic or other limitations or preferences. All visitors to the Site (including non-registered visitors) can view a Support Worker’s profile, except their contact details, which are only available to registered HireUp Clients.  
iii. Information in your profile is also available in search results. 

Making contact with Users  
HireUp is a new, innovative and highly cost-effective form of online, digital employment agency which, for a fee payable to HireUp by Clients, helps Clients find, interview and personally choose the care worker/s they wish to employ.  
In return for the fee payable to HireUp by Clients, HireUp will undertake all necessary “backroom” administration and payroll services, including managing payroll transactions, calculating, deducting and remitting to the Australian Tax Office all necessary taxation and compulsory superannuation contributions, and providing Workers Compensation insurance coverage for all Support Workers.  
It is the responsibility of the individual User to make contact with other Users with whom they wish to communicate. By joining this Site, you agree to allow other users to view your contact details and make contact with you. HireUp will share email and telephone details with other site Users to allow them to contact you. By registering on this Site, you give permission to fellow users to contact you at a time and in a manner that they see fit.

Feedback  
If you contact us to give us feedback, register a complaint or ask questions about the Site or Services, we may store your communications, including any personal information you include, so we can effectively respond to you.

### Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information

Non-personal information is information that does not identify the specific User. This type of information may include things like the URL of the website you visited before and after visiting our Site, the type of browser you are using, and the IP address of the computer you use to visit the Site.  
i. Cookies. We collect some anonymous information about how you use the Site by setting and accessing cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer. These cookies track information such as how often you visit the Site, what pages you view, and where you go after you leave the Site. The cookies track your computer, not you. They are not connected to any personal information about you. If you choose to disable a cookie, you may not be able to use certain features of the Site.  
ii. Activity and Log Data. We automatically store information related to your use of the Site in our log files, such as the pages you view on the Site, your browser type, IP address, operating system, referring URL and the date and time of your visit. We use this type of information to administer the Site and to analyze trends. This information is not tied to personally identifiable information.

### Disclosure of Your Information to Third Parties

Disclosure by law; Protection of Us and Others.  
We may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law, at the request of a third party, or if we, in our sole discretion, believe that disclosure is reasonable to:  
1\. Comply with the law, requests or orders from law enforcement, or any legal process (whether or not such disclosure is required by applicable law)  
2\. Protect or defend our or a third party’s rights or property  
3\. Protect someone’s health or safety, such as when harm or violence against any person is threatened.  
Service Providers - We may share your personal information with companies that perform services for us, such as analyzing customer data, providing marketing assistance, and processing credit card payments. These companies have access to personal information as needed to perform their functions, but may not disclose personal information for other purposes.  
Business Changes - We may share your information with any parent company, subsidiary, joint ventures or other companies under a common control that we may have now or in the future, in which case, we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires our company or all or substantially all of our assets, that company will own your information and will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Updating and Correcting Information

If you need to change your personal information, you may update or correct this information  
by logging into your account and accessing the “Profile” section within your account. We encourage you to make any updates required to your personal information promptly. 

###  Your Choices

You may opt-out of receiving promotional emails from us at any time, by using the link on the bottom of every promotional email you receive from HireUp. Please note you cannot opt-out of receiving administrative and transaction-related emails from us. These are emails that relate to your account or your activity on the Site.

###  Security of Information 

Security of your personal information is vital, and HireUp takes precautions to protect it. However no method of data transmission over the Internet or data storage is 100% secure and therefore, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of any information transmitted to or from the Site.

###  Age Restrictions 

The Site is not intended for use by persons under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under 18, and no part of the Site is designed to attract anyone under the age of 18. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information, please contact us. If we become aware that an individual under 18 has opened an account and provided us with personal information, we will remove such information and terminate that person’s account.

###  Changes to Our Privacy Policy 

We may revise our Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the Privacy Policy will govern our use of your information and will always be located on this webpage. If we make a change to our Privacy Policy that is material, we will notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes before implementing the change on the Site and/or via the email associated with your account. By continuing to access the Site and use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

###  Contact Us 

If you have any feedback, questions or complaints about this Privacy Policy or any of our privacy-related practices, please contact us directly.
